Leigh Ann Stuart

4211 Buckhead Ridge Rd., Happy Valley, TN 37878 Las2001@gmail.com (999) 121-2323

PROFILE

Enthusiastic retail Store manager with two years of experience managing a busy retail venue generating \$1M in revenue. Focuses on empowering employees to serve customers and each other with integrity and excellence. Currently studying for a degree in retail management.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Store Manager

Harmony Music & Games, Happy Valley, TN | September 2018 - Present

- Supervise 65 team members, set schedules and enforce company policies in hiring and firing
- Hold regular mini-sessions (two per month) on customer service and self-improvement
- Resolve customer grievances to foster customer satisfaction and loyalty
- Cover work shifts for absent team members
- Trained team members to increase sales revenue from \$500,000 to \$1M in 2019
- Created budgets that saved 13% on operating costs in 2019

Team Member

Harmony Music & Games, Happy Valley, TN | July 2016 - September 2018

- Greeted and assisted approximately 150 customers per shift, helping them locate items and making upsell and cross-sell recommendations
- Completed purchases and loyalty club applications
- Organized and restocked merchandise in heavy traffic areas to drive product sales
- Processed POS transactions, including cash, check and credit purchases and refunds
- Reconciled cash drawer at beginning and end of each shift and resolved discrepancies
- Performed opening and closing procedures according to store policies

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Business Administration; Retail Management

Strayer University **(Online)** January 2019 - Present

High School Diploma

Happy Valley Senior High School Happy Valley, TN, 2016

KEY SKILLS

- Customer assistance
- Collaboration and motivation
- Training and coaching
- Delegation
- Sales planning
- Cash drawer management
- Inventory management